<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<godaddy>
<coupon>
	<amount>35</amount>
	<title>35% Off New Products</title>
	<expiration>08/31/17</expiration>
	<code>CJCRMN35</code>
	<description>Save 35% on new products. Exclusions apply. See site for details.</description>
	<details> Not applicable to ICANN fees, taxes, transfers, bulk pricing, premium domains, premium templates, Search Engine Visibility advertising budget, gift cards or Sunrise/Landrush registration or pre-registration fees. Offer good towards new product purchases only and cannot be used on product renewals. Cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer, sale, discount or promotion. After the initial purchase term, discounted products will renew at the then current renewal list price.</details>
	<url>godaddy.com</url>
</coupon>
<coupon>
	<amount>93</amount>
	<title>93% Off! .COM Domains for Just $0.99*!</title>
	<expiration>08/31/17</expiration>
	<code>CJCRMN99U</code>
	<description>Save 93% on a .COM domain for just $0.99! Limit one per customer. Good in the US and Canada only. Not valid on renewals.* Exclusions apply</description>
	<details>Plus ICANN fee of $0.18 per domain name per year. $1.99 price for the first year of one new or transfer .COM per customer. Additional years or .COMs may be purchased for$9.99* per year. Discounts cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer or promotion. Customers may not use gift cards, In-Store Credit, CCAvenue, Skrill, PayPal® or AliPay to redeem this offer. Your discount will be applied in your shopping cart. After the initial purchase term, discounted products will renew at the then-current renewal list price. Go Daddy reserves the right to deny use of this offer and/or cancel domains purchased using this offer if the offer is abused or used fraudulently, as determined by Go Daddy in its sole discretion. Not valid on renewals.</details>
	<url>godaddy.com</url>
</coupon>
<coupon>
	<amount>87</amount>
	<title>87% Off .COM Domains + $2 Private Registration, Only $4</title>
	<expiration>08/31/17</expiration>
	<code>cjcrmn2cp</code>
	<description>Save 87% Off .COM Domains + $2 Private Registration - $24.98 value for $4. Exclusions apply. See site for details.</description>
	<details>*Plus ICANN fee of $0.18 per domain name per year. $2.00 price good for the first year of one new .COM per customer; not valid for transfers or renewals. Additional years or .COMs may be purchased for $9.99 per year. $2.00 privacy offer valid for entire initial registration term of the domain name. When the domain name renews, each year of private registration will renew at the regular rates in effect at the time of renewal. Discounts cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer or promotion. Customers may not use gift cards, PayPal, Skrill, In-Store Credit or AliPay to redeem this offer. Your discount will be applied in your shopping cart.</details>
	<url>godaddy.com</url>
</coupon>
<coupon>
	<amount>85</amount>
	<title>85% Off 12 Months Economy Hosting - $1 Per Month</title>
	<expiration>08/31/17</expiration>
	<code>cjcrmn1hos</code>
	<description>Get 12 months of Economy Web Hosting for just $1/month, an 85% Savings! Excludes renewals.</description>
	<details>Plus ICANN fee of $0.18 per domain name per year. Price applies to first year only of one new registration per customer; not valid for transfer or renewals. Discounts cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer, sale, discount or promotion. After the initial purchase term, discounted products will renew at the then-current renewal list price.</details>
	<url>godaddy.com</url>
</coupon>

</godaddy>